hostbasket.com 2002-12-02

# Hostbasket - Configure the hosting solution YOU need

|  | 

We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your expectation that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting our Web site or by otherwise interacting with one of our Services, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

##  What Information Do We Collect? 

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way, such as by telephone or by electronic mail.  This information includes your full name, company name, mailing address, phone number, email address, facsimile number. 

##  Do We Share the Information We Receive ? 

When registering a domain name for you, we have to provide your full name, company name, mailing address, phone number, email address and your facsimile number, as well as the creation and expiration dates of your domain name registration and the nameserver information associated with your domain name, to the registrar executing the actual registration. This information is stored in a Whois database and is available to the public via an interactive Web page and a "port 43" WHOIS service. Please note that we may not be able to control how members of the public may use the WHOIS Information. 

If you have opted-into receiving information about products and services provided by our partners and affiliates, we will share your name, address, phone number, email address, in addition to information provided by you in response to our opt-in survey, so that our partners and affiliates may contact you regarding the products and services in which you have expressed interest. 

##  How Secure Is Information About Me ? 

We work with Worldpay for processing of online payment. Worldpay protects the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We do not keep credit card information in our databases, and we do not receive credit card information from Worldpay. Worldpay only provides us with customer details and payment status. You can further help to ensure your security by taking a few simple precautions. For instance, it is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your username and password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

##  What Information Can I Access ? 

We give you access to certain information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. To view or change this information, login to your account. When you update information, in some cases we keep a copy of the prior version for our records. 

##  Sites Other Than Ours 

Although we are committed to protecting your privacy, not all other Web sites are as conscientious. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the content or privacy policies of other Web sites including those of advertisers to which it may link and those which link to us. This Privacy Notice applies only to the information collected by this Web site. We ask that you review the privacy policies of every online service you use before submitting personal information. 

##  Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions 

If you choose to visit our Web site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Services Agreement, including limitations on damages, and application of the law. If you have any concern about privacy, please contact us and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Services Agreement will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. 

back 

|
